[dotenv@17.3.1] injecting env (0) from .env -- tip: ≡ƒñû agentic secret storage: https://dotenvx.com/as2
Name of the panel valuer
Name of the party/owner
Address of the property
Name/s of the Reported owner/ name/s of persons in whose names/s the property registered and address
Purpose of valuation
List of documents produced for perusal
Date of inspection
Date of valuation
Approximate Distance from the branch to the property
Situation/location/brief description of the land / site
Lat & long
Google Map Link
Boundary Details of the Property as per Document
Boundary Details of the Property as per Site
Assuming the entire property is let out, the probable monthly rent and advance
Whether the building plan has been approved?
If yes, date of approval, approving authority, and whether the building has been constructed as per the approved plan at the time of inspection
If no, the reason for non-approval
General Remarks
The total area (Extent of the site/Land)
Description of the site/land
Character of locality
Class of locality
Classification
Development of surrounding areas
Is the locality subjected to frequent flooding
Feasibility to the civil amenities like schools, hospital, offices, market etc.
Shape of land
Type of use to which it can be put
Any other restriction of usage
Nature of right, whether lease hold
Road facility
Is it a corner plot
Lift
Carpark
Water supply/potentiality
Underground sewerage system
Any other sentimental social issue Which may affect the value.
Type of construction
Quality of construction
Appearance of the building
Number of floors
Maintenance of the building
Description of the building
Area Details
Foundation
Superstructure
Roof
Doors
Windows
Age of the building
Estimated further life of the building
Depreciation
Replacement Rate of Building
Extent of Land as per deed
Extent of Land as per Patta
Extent of Land for Valuation
Extent of Building for Valuation
Guideline Value of Property per Sq Ft
Prevailing unit market rate of land
Adopted rate of valuation
Building Valuation
Remarks about the property
Land Extent
Building Extent
Guide Line Value
Guide Line Value of Land
Guideline Value of Building
Guide Line Value of Property
Adopted Market Value of Land
Value of Land
Value of Building
Total Value of Property
Total Property
Fair Market Value of the above said property
Realizable Sale Value
Distress Sale Value
Total Guideline Value of the above said property
Enclosures
GEO-CO ORDINATES
Reference Number
Valuer Name
Pursuant to the request from
Branch
Purpose of Valuation
Date of Inspection
Date of Valuation
Proposed Owner of the property
List of documents produced for perusal:
Landmark of the property
Plot Number
Door Number
Survey No / T.S. No / Ward No.
Street Name
Village
Taluk
Place and District, State
Is the property situated
Classification of the area
Boundaries of the Property
If no, the reason for non- approval
Shape of Land
Feasibility to the civil amenities like Schools, hospital, offices, market etc.
Any other sentimental social issue Which may affect the value
Year of Construction
Age of building
Future Life expectancy
No. of Floors
Covered area Floor wise
Walls (Load Bearing / Partition)
Flooring
Painting
Compound Wall
Electrical arrangement
Water supply arrangements
Sanitary Arrangements
Condition Exterior
Condition Interior
Present Stage of Construction
Development works to the land
Property presently occupied by
General narrative description covering other points if any
VALUATION
Considered Extent of Land for Valuation
Considered Extent of Building for Valuation
Plinth area
Adopted Guideline Value of land
Total Guideline Value of Land
Total Market Value of Land
Total Market Value of Building
=Add( a+b+c+d+e+f+g)
Market Value of Building
Realizable Sale Value %
Distress Sale Value %
The Guideline value of the Property
= Add (E+Add( a+b+c+d+e+f+g))
The Market Value of the Property
= Add ( F+Add( a+b+c+d+e+f+g))
The Realizable Sale Value of property
= Add ( F+Add( a+b+c+d+e+f+g))*J%
The Distress Sale Value of the property
= Add Add ( F+Add( a+b+c+d+e+f+g))*K%
<Geolocation
