All labels:
0 Name of the panel valuer
1 Name of the party/owner
2 Address of the property
3 Name/s of the Reported owner/ name/s of persons in whose names/s the property registered and address
4 Purpose of valuation
5 List of documents produced for perusal
6 Date of inspection
7 Date of valuation
8 Approximate Distance from the branch to the property
9 Situation/location/brief description of the land / site
10 Lat & long
11 Google Map Link
12 Boundary Details of the Property as per Document
13 Boundary Details of the Property as per Site
14 Assuming the entire property is let out, the probable monthly rent and advance
15 Whether the building plan has been approved?
16 If yes, date of approval, approving authority, and whether the building has been constructed as per the approved plan at the time of inspection
17 If no, the reason for non-approval
18 General Remarks
19 The total area (Extent of the site/Land)
20 Description of the site/land
21 Character of locality
22 Class of locality
23 Classification
24 Development of surrounding areas
25 Is the locality subjected to frequent flooding
26 Feasibility to the civil amenities like schools, hospital, offices, market etc.
27 Shape of land
28 Type of use to which it can be put
29 Any other restriction of usage
30 Nature of right, whether lease hold
31 Road facility
32 Is it a corner plot
33 Lift
34 Carpark
35 Water supply/potentiality
36 Underground sewerage system
37 Any other sentimental social issue Which may affect the value.
38 Type of construction
39 Quality of construction
40 Appearance of the building
41 Number of floors
42 Maintenance of the building
43 Description of the building
44 Area Details
45 Foundation
46 Superstructure
47 Roof
48 Doors
49 Windows
50 Age of the building
51 Estimated further life of the building
52 Depreciation
53 Replacement Rate of Building
54 Extent of Land as per deed
55 Extent of Land as per Patta
56 Extent of Land for Valuation
57 Extent of Building for Valuation
58 Guideline Value of Property per Sq Ft
59 Prevailing unit market rate of land
60 Adopted rate of valuation
61 Building Valuation
62 Remarks about the property
63 Land Extent
64 Building Extent
65 Guide Line Value
66 Guide Line Value of Land
67 Guideline Value of Building
68 Guide Line Value of Property
69 Adopted Market Value of Land
70 Value of Land
71 Value of Building
72 Total Value of Property
73 Total Property
74 Fair Market Value of the above said property
75 Realizable Sale Value
76 Distress Sale Value
77 Total Guideline Value of the above said property
78 Enclosures
79 GEO-CO ORDINATES
